<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>posts on Dylan Meeus</title>
    <link>https://dylanmeeus.github.io/categories/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in posts on Dylan Meeus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 23:50:07 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dylanmeeus.github.io/categories/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Audio From Scratch: Part 3</title>
      <link>https://dylanmeeus.github.io/posts/audio-from-scratch-pt3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 23:50:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dylanmeeus.github.io/posts/audio-from-scratch-pt3/</guid>
      <description>Insert Lead paragraph here.
A augue nunc lacus auctor efficitur tempor placerat, dictum volutpat mi vitae viverra porta non sem, himenaeos senectus vivamus potenti cubilia sollicitudin. Curae cursus inceptos tincidunt magna mi nibh ad enim etiam, molestie eu quis primis hendrerit taciti phasellus. Feugiat ultricies dictumst iaculis potenti odio laoreet urna at, ultrices curae leo accumsan proin sem lobortis.
Heading 2 Sollicitudin ornare odio blandit aenean enim lacus accumsan elementum vestibulum porta mauris lorem, ullamcorper class fermentum sem hendrerit ante augue penatibus scelerisque felis leo proin,ad nascetur venenatis sodales dignissim viverra suspendisse turpis convallis condimentum sapien.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audio From Scratch: Part2, Anatomy of a wave (file)</title>
      <link>https://dylanmeeus.github.io/posts/audio-from-scratch-pt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 19:15:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dylanmeeus.github.io/posts/audio-from-scratch-pt2/</guid>
      <description>In our last post we have looked at how we can create a simple binary sound file. By creating a sine wave with exponential decay, we can get the effect of a single note playing.
It&amp;rsquo;s good to know what these types of files look like. In the real world however you&amp;rsquo;ll usually encounter files that are a bit more complex. One of the common formats to find audio in is the WAVE file format, normally denoted with the extension .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audio From Scratch: Part 1, generating sounds</title>
      <link>https://dylanmeeus.github.io/posts/audio-from-scratch-pt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 18:43:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dylanmeeus.github.io/posts/audio-from-scratch-pt1/</guid>
      <description>Audio from scratch: generating sound In my &amp;lsquo;audio from scratch&amp;rsquo; series we will take a look at various ways in which we can manipulate audio data with Go. We&amp;rsquo;ll look at the anatomy of a wave file, how to apply stereo panning, converting mono files to stereo, how to work with breakpoint files through linear interpolation, etc.
But, in this post we’ll be using Go to create sound from scratch in binary format.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>